<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>netzap.xyz</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on netzap.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why is Salesforce Industries a big deal?</title>
      <link>/2021/11/04/sfi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/11/04/sfi/</guid>
      <description>Salesforce is bringing in new tools to help businesses achieve quicker value while reducing the cost to build solutions. Salesforce is using industry specific clouds that add to the Salesforce platform with smart defaults which help propel solutions forward.
Salesforce started (and still advertises itself) as a CRM platform on the cloud. Over the years, Salesforce has acquired new tools and companies that help extend its margin of innovation from its competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>privacy policy</title>
      <link>/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy Last updated: January 23, 2022 | Latest Version is hosted at: External Privacy Policy Link
This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.
We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top/about/</guid>
      <description>netzap.xyz is a collection of Salesforce.com implementation notes and patterns as we learn them. It is meant as a reference for the future us, implementers and clients evaluating a Salesforce.com implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/top/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top/links/</guid>
      <description>Useful Links </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts Archive</title>
      <link>/top/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top/archive/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
